Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Grievance Records, Series 2
  - Grievance Committee agendas and minutes, Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/3], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/3], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [3/3], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [1/2], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee [2/2], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota/South Dakota Joint State Grievance Committee, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota Joint State Grievance Committee, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Petrolem Carriers Group State Committee, 1971-1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - National Grievance Committee, 1977-1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1971; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin Joint Auto Transport Committee, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Company grievance records, Series 2 Subseries 2
    - A.B.F. Freight System, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - A.I.M. Drivers, Incorporated, 1983-1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - A.N.R. Freight System, Incorporated, 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Abraham Transfer, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Ace Lines, Incorporated, 1978-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated, 1974-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Ag Processing, 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Ahmann Transfer, 1972; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Allstate Transportation Company, 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Applied Texture, Incorporated, 1983-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Armour Food Company, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Aslesens Company, 1978-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Associated Milk Producers, Incorporated, 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - August Deike Transfer, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Barber Transportation Company, 1979-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Barrett Moving and Storage, 1981-1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Bay and Bay Transfer Company, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Beatrice Meats, Incorporated/Swift-Eckrich, 1977-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Bell Cold Storage Company, 1979-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Beltman North American Company, 1973-1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Berger Transfer and Storage Company, 1981-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Britton Motor Service, Incorporated, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Bryan Fisher, Incorporated, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Burlington-Northern Air Freight, Incorporated, 1983-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - C.A.T. Worldwide Moving and Storage, 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Campbell Soup Company [1/2], 1985-1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Campbell Soup Company [2/2], 1992-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Capp Homes, 1975-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Century-Mercury Motor Freight, 1974-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Clark Transport Company, Incorporated, 1976-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Commerce Freight Terminals, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Freightways, Incorporated, 1978-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Continental Minnesota, Incorporated, 1977-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - County of Nobles, 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Creamette Company, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Culligan Water Conditioning Company, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Dahlen Transport, 1975-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Driver Power, Incorporated, 1976-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Edgecomb Metals Company, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation, 1973-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Furnell and Webb Transfer Company, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - G.M.W., Incorporated, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Gateway Foods [1/2], 1981-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Gateway Foods [2/2], 1982-1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Glendenning Motorways, Incorporated, 1978-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Greif Brothers Corporation, 1968-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - H. Brooks and Company, 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Hankin Transportation, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Hayes Insulation Company, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Heartland Food Company, 1989-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Henry Lambert Trucking Company, 1976-1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated, 1982-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Interstate Brands Corporation, 2002-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - J&J Transfer Company, 1975-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Jacobson Transfer Company, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Janesville Auto Transport Company, 1979-1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - John Sexton and Company, 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - KNUJ/KXLP, Incorporated, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Kelly Transfer, Incorporated, 1977-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Kenosha Auto Transport Company, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - LaBelle Storage and Moving Company, 1975-1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - LaSalle Cartage Company, Incorporated, 1978-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Lambert Trucking Company, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Landry Transfer, Incorporated, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Landy Packing Company, 1979-1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Larson Warehouse, 1975-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - M.F. Bank and Company, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Maiers Transfer and Storage Company, Incorporated, 1973-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Marigold Foods, Incorporated, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - May Company, 1978-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - McKesson Chemical Company, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Transfermen's Association, Incorporated, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Midwest Driver Corporation, 1974-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Midwest Haulers, Incorporated, 1967-1975; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Milwaukee Motor Transportation Company, 1978-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Minneapolis Household Goods Movers Association, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Minneapolis Van and Warehouse Company, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Minnesota Express, Incorporated, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Minnesota-Wisconsin Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Mix Transfer Company, 1979-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Montgomery Ward and Company, Incorporated, 1987-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Murphy Delivery Service, Incorporated, 1974-1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Murphy Warehouse Company [1/3], 1976-1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Murphy Warehouse Company [2/3], 1979-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Murphy Warehouse Company [3/3], 1983-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - National Drivers, Incorporated, 1974-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - National Food Stores, Incorporated, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - National Super Markets, Incorporated, 1980-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - National Tea Company, 1979-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Neptune World Wide Moving, Incorporated, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Neuendorf Transportation Company, 1979-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - New Ulm Concrete Products, Incorporated, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - New Ulm Wholesale, Incorporated, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - North Star Concrete Company, 1980-1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Northern Cargo Association, 1980-1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Northwest Transfer, 1979-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - OCHS Brick and Tile Company, 1992-1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated [1/5], 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated [2/5], 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated [3/5], 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated [4/5], 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor, Incorporated [5/5], 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Gamble Robinson Company, 1977-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.), 1974-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Pennant Food Company, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Perkins Motor Transport, 1963-1964; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Perlman Rocque Company, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Pictsweet Frozen Foods, Incorporated, 1990-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Pillsbury Company, 1974-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Preferred Products, Incorporated, 1978-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Quality Electric Steel Casings, Incorporated, 1970-1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Quickie Transport Company, 1963-1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Rapidways Truck Leasing, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Raymond Motor Transport Company, Incorporated, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated, 1977-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Roadway Express, Incorporated, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Rocket Transfer, 1974-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Ruan Transport, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - S.A.L. Cartage, 1978-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Security Warehouse, 1975-1976; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated, 1981-2003; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Skellet Van and Storage Company, 1978-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Sky and Land Express, 1980-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Smith's Transfer Corporation, 1972-1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Space Center, Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Stemm Transfer and Storage Company, 1976-1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Cartage Company, 1974-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Stinar Corporation, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated, 1971-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Super Valu Stores, Incorporated, 1982-1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Superior Concrete Block, Incorporated, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Swift Dairy and Poultry Company, 1977-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Terry Brothers, Incorporated, 1974-1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Systems, Incorporated, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Trucking, Incorporated, 1980-1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Tyson Truck Lines, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - United Foods, Incorporated, 1983-1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [1/4], 1974-1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [2/4], 1978-1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [3/4], 1979-1980; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [4/4], 1980-1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - United Van Bus Delivery, Marathon Division, 1986-1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Van den Bergh Foods Company, 1991-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Wallner Construction Company, Incorporated, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Ward Transfer, Incorporated, 1975-1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Wholesale Produce Supply Company, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Wintz Parcel Service, 1980-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Wis-Pak, Incorporated, 1973-2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - World Wide, Incorporated, 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Worthington Regional Hospital, 1983-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Yellow Freight System, Incorporated, 1983-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Company Records, Series 3; 0 Linear Feet
  This series is divided into two subseries: Correspondence, handbooks, policy information; Employee records. Folders are arranged alphabetically by company name.
  The materials of this series include correspondence, handbooks, policy information, and employee records including employment history, seniority status, and medical records. They range in date from 1961-2012.
  - Correspondence, handbooks, policy information, Series 3 Subseries 1
    - 3M Company, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - A.B.F. Freight System, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - A.B.I. Machinery Movers, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - A.I.M. Drivers, Incorporated, 1982-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - A.N.R. Freight System, 1986-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - A.R.A. Services, Incorporated, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Abraham Transfer, 1972-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Ace Lines, Incorporated, 1970-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Acme Transfer and Storage Company, 1976-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [1/5], 1976-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [2/5], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [3/5], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [4/5], 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [5/5], 1986-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Ag Processing, Incorporated, 1985-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Agora Distribution, Incorporated, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Ahmann Transfer, 1963-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Air Express International Corporation, 1976-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Allstate Transportation Company, 1979-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Alltemp Distribution Company, 1985-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - American Freight System, Incorporated [1/2], 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - American Freight Systems, Incorporated [2/2], 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Applied Texture, Incorporated, 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Armour Food Company [1/2], 1968-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Armour Food Company [2/2], 1983-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Arrow Motor Freight, 1969-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Aslesens Company, 1978-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Associated Milk Producers, Incorporated, 1996-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Atlas Plastics Corporation, 1979-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - August Deike Transfer, 1983-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - B.N. Transport, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Banquet Foods Corporation, 1975-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Barber Transportation Company, 1968-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Barrett Moving and Storing, 1982-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Barry Cartage Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Bay and Bay Transfer Company, 1973-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Beatrice Meats/Swift-Eckrich, 1984-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Beaver Transport Company, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Beckman Produce, Incorporated, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Bell Cold Storage Company, 1979-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Beltmann North American Company, 1974-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Ben Franklin Drivers, 1975-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Berger Transfer and Storage Company, 1974-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Bergin Wholesale Fruit Company, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Better Home Deliveries, Incorporated [1/3], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Better Home Deliveries, Incorporated [2/3], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Better Home Deliveries, Incorporated [3/3], 1983-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Bix Fruit Company, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Brainerd Recreational Supply, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Brede Convention Drayage, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Briggs Transportation Company [1/2], 1980-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Briggs Transportation Company [2/2], 1983-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Bryan Fisher, Incorporated, 1981-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Burlington-Northern Air Freight, Incorporated, 1978-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - CFS Continental, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Cable Value Network, 1987-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Caldwell Packing, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Campbell Soup Company [1/5], 1976-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Campbell Soup Company [2/5], 1989-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Campbell Soup Company [3/5], 1993-1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Campbell Soup Company [4/5], 1994-1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Campbell Soup Company [5/5], 1995-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Capp Homes [1/2], 1973-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Capp Homes [2/2], 1978-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Carpenter Transfer, Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Ceco Corporation, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Century Mercury Motor Frieght, Incorporated, 1975-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Champion International Corporation, 1975-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Avenue Transfer, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Churchill Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - City of Worthington [1/2], 1975-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - City of Worthington [2/2], 1980-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - City Transfer Industries, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Clark Transport Company, Incorporated, 1975-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Clear View Optical, Incorporated [1/2], 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Clear View Optical, Incorporated [2/2], 1984-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Commerce Freight Terminals, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Consolidated Freightways, Incorporated, 1975-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Continental Minnesota, Incorporated, 1976-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Conway Central Express, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Cotter and Company, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - County of Nobles [1/4], 1980-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - County of Nobles [2/4], 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 1)